while we work hard towards a financially
secured and worry-free retirement we
also look to leaving a positive Legacy
to our next Generation do we have to
sacrifice one aspiration for the other
at FWD we firmly believe that you
shouldn't have to choose between the two
this is why we created a plan that lets
you enjoy your retirement and leave a
lasting Legacy for your future
Generations we call it FWD life income a
participating whole life plan that
provides a stream of passive income that
lasts beyond your lifetime receive
regular cash benefits as your retirement
income and have your loved ones continue
receiving these benefits for the
generations to come a plan designed to
give greater Financial Security with the
highest guaranteed cash benefit and
total accumulated maturity values
offered in the current market in
addition receive a guaranteed special
benefit which is six percent of some
assured at the 25th month of the policy
take charge of your aspiration with a
single premium from fifty thousand
dollars or a monthly premium of 250 over
a 10-year premium term FWD life income a
plan that empowers you to have it all
enjoy a worry-free retirement and leave
a lasting Financial Legacy for your
future Generations speak to any of our
financial advisory Partners today to
find out more
foreign
[Music]